[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "So what's your name?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "'s", "your", "name", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Nicole.", "answer_tokens": ["Nicole", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "Do you have a question for me?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "question", "for", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "New Jersey.", "answer_tokens": ["New", "Jersey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "How did your house get broken?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "your", "house", "get", "broken", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "By the storm.", "answer_tokens": ["By", "the", "storm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Have you got new ones?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "got", "new", "ones", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nicole"]}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Are you directing for me?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "directing", "for", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "You keep going, Nicole.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "keep", "going", ",", "Nicole", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Are you angry that nothing more has been done from this time of period?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "angry", "that", "nothing", "more", "has", "been", "done", "from", "this", "time", "of", "period", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "JJR", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "It's incredibly frustrating.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "incredibly", "frustrating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Do you think he will?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "will", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Do you still have confidence in him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "have", "confidence", "in", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "I think that we watch him a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "we", "watch", "him", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Nicole, do you like being on TV?", "question_tokens": ["Nicole", ",", "do", "you", "like", "being", "on", "TV", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Will you do that for me?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "do", "that", "for", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "When.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Would you like that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "And some bath toys.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "some", "bath", "toys", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Have you been taken aback by the scale of venom that's come your way?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "taken", "aback", "by", "the", "scale", "of", "venom", "that", "'s", "come", "your", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "You know, it's not, mostly it's been supportive.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "not", ",", "mostly", "it", "'s", "been", "supportive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "CD", "WDT", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "How much of that criticism if you're wearing your Mike Rowe Man of the People hat is valid?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "that", "criticism", "if", "you", "'re", "wearing", "your", "Mike", "Rowe", "Man", "of", "the", "People", "hat", "is", "valid", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "I've only got the one hat, and so for what it's worth, I would say all criticism is valid.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "only", "got", "the", "one", "hat", ",", "and", "so", "for", "what", "it", "'s", "worth", ",", "I", "would", "say", "all", "criticism", "is", "valid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike Rowe Man"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "And do you still sing opera?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "still", "sing", "opera", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Weddings, funerals.", "answer_tokens": ["Weddings", ",", "funerals", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "A burst?", "question_tokens": ["A", "burst", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Again, just for my benefit, can you do the \"Jaws One\" just when you thought you're safe to get back into the water?", "question_tokens": ["Again", ",", "just", "for", "my", "benefit", ",", "can", "you", "do", "the", "``", "Jaws", "One", "''", "just", "when", "you", "thought", "you", "'re", "safe", "to", "get", "back", "into", "the", "water", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "``", "VBZ", "CD", "''", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Just when you thought it was safe to go back in Piers' show, the questions begun again, it'll scare the crap out of you.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "when", "you", "thought", "it", "was", "safe", "to", "go", "back", "in", "Piers", "'", "show", ",", "the", "questions", "begun", "again", ",", "it", "'ll", "scare", "the", "crap", "out", "of", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ford"]}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "``", "JJ", "NNS", "''", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 274, "question": "So you have just -- you've just finished with Ford, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "have", "just", "--", "you", "'ve", "just", "finished", "with", "Ford", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "I'm finished with Ford, I'm finished with \"Dirty Jobs\", really I mean ...", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "finished", "with", "Ford", ",", "I", "'m", "finished", "with", "``", "Dirty", "Jobs", "''", ",", "really", "I", "mean", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ford"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Are you actually unemployed right now?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "actually", "unemployed", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "I'm unemployed for the first time in my adult life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "unemployed", "for", "the", "first", "time", "in", "my", "adult", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", ",", "``", "UH", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "How does it feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "it", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "You know, it's odd but I mean seriously it forces you to step back and go, \"OK.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "odd", "but", "I", "mean", "seriously", "it", "forces", "you", "to", "step", "back", "and", "go", ",", "``", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["BlackBerry Messenger"]}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Did you just say BM?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "just", "say", "BM", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "BBM the BlackBerry Messenger.", "answer_tokens": ["BBM", "the", "BlackBerry", "Messenger", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "You know what that is?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "that", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Do you understand how a company can be valued like that when it only employs like under 100 people?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "how", "a", "company", "can", "be", "valued", "like", "that", "when", "it", "only", "employs", "like", "under", "100", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Actually, I mean I think I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "I", "mean", "I", "think", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Simple as that?", "question_tokens": ["Simple", "as", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Well, what do you say on this debate?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "do", "you", "say", "on", "this", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "I mean, I would say there's a third observation too which is it's either a willing thing that you do because you believe its good business, or because you're just an altruistic soul, or it's something that you're compelled to do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "would", "say", "there", "'s", "a", "third", "observation", "too", "which", "is", "it", "'s", "either", "a", "willing", "thing", "that", "you", "do", "because", "you", "believe", "its", "good", "business", ",", "or", "because", "you", "'re", "just", "an", "altruistic", "soul", ",", "or", "it", "'s", "something", "that", "you", "'re", "compelled", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "The American dream that I guess helped you become the man you are and the success that you've been, is that dream still obtainable in the same way or has it changed?", "question_tokens": ["The", "American", "dream", "that", "I", "guess", "helped", "you", "become", "the", "man", "you", "are", "and", "the", "success", "that", "you", "'ve", "been", ",", "is", "that", "dream", "still", "obtainable", "in", "the", "same", "way", "or", "has", "it", "changed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Oh man.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "What is the one job you will least regret not having to do again?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "one", "job", "you", "will", "least", "regret", "not", "having", "to", "do", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Least regret not having to do again.", "answer_tokens": ["Least", "regret", "not", "having", "to", "do", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "What was the single worst thing you ever did in the whole lot of series (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "single", "worst", "thing", "you", "ever", "did", "in", "the", "whole", "lot", "of", "series", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "So, there's a thing called a lift pump.", "answer_tokens": ["So", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "thing", "called", "a", "lift", "pump", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "I mean, really, I wouldn't play out?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "really", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "play", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "I'll tell you what, stay here.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "what", ",", "stay", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "``", "VBN", "NNS", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 365, "question": "What do you know about this and how serious you think it is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "know", "about", "this", "and", "how", "serious", "you", "think", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "I think it's -- any threat of course is serious and this is exacerbated by the fact that we are seeing the spread of al-Qaeda or al-Qaeda \"affiliated organizations.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "--", "any", "threat", "of", "course", "is", "serious", "and", "this", "is", "exacerbated", "by", "the", "fact", "that", "we", "are", "seeing", "the", "spread", "of", "al-Qaeda", "or", "al-Qaeda", "``", "affiliated", "organizations", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "What is the solution here senator, do you think, to what is clearly a massive problem that's finally erupted in the way that we've seen?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "solution", "here", "senator", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "to", "what", "is", "clearly", "a", "massive", "problem", "that", "'s", "finally", "erupted", "in", "the", "way", "that", "we", "'ve", "seen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Serious sanctions.", "answer_tokens": ["Serious", "sanctions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Any improvement there or is it the situation worsening?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "improvement", "there", "or", "is", "it", "the", "situation", "worsening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "CCAIN: It's worsening.", "answer_tokens": ["CCAIN", ":", "It", "'s", "worsening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "It's just -- it's a free country but that kind of language really doesn't have any place in our political dialog.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "free", "country", "but", "that", "kind", "of", "language", "really", "does", "n't", "have", "any", "place", "in", "our", "political", "dialog", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["National Security"], "LOCATION": ["Texas", "United States"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Should he now distance himself completely from Ted Nugent because of this comment?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "he", "now", "distance", "himself", "completely", "from", "Ted", "Nugent", "because", "of", "this", "comment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "Well, if I were him, because those comments, I would, but because I don't think the people of Texas -- look, I am a severe critic of President Obama particularly on National Security but that kind of language, he's the president of United States, he's been elected and reelected and I believe we should treat him respectfully.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "I", "were", "him", ",", "because", "those", "comments", ",", "I", "would", ",", "but", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "the", "people", "of", "Texas", "--", "look", ",", "I", "am", "a", "severe", "critic", "of", "President", "Obama", "particularly", "on", "National", "Security", "but", "that", "kind", "of", "language", ",", "he", "'s", "the", "president", "of", "United", "States", ",", "he", "'s", "been", "elected", "and", "reelected", "and", "I", "believe", "we", "should", "treat", "him", "respectfully", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Nugent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "What do you make of those comments?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "those", "comments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "It's a free country.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "free", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Does it sting?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "sting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "As a human being, I can't control what they say, how they behave.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "a", "human", "being", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "control", "what", "they", "say", ",", "how", "they", "behave", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Do you think he could win a nomination by playing that card?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "could", "win", "a", "nomination", "by", "playing", "that", "card", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Is Chris Christie still a potential serious candidate despite everything has happened?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "Chris", "Christie", "still", "a", "potential", "serious", "candidate", "despite", "everything", "has", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "I believe so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Who are you anyway, Daniel Fruik?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "you", "anyway", ",", "Daniel", "Fruik", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "But right now, he's sitting home having a parade for himself.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "right", "now", ",", "he", "'s", "sitting", "home", "having", "a", "parade", "for", "himself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Daniel Fruik"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "That's you, right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "you", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Yes, that's me.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Did you guys know that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "guys", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I do now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "What do you think is being the reason?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "is", "being", "the", "reason", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Well, that's a good question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "And Phil, for more logistical and technical point of view, how difficult was it to create animated Lego?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Phil", ",", "for", "more", "logistical", "and", "technical", "point", "of", "view", ",", "how", "difficult", "was", "it", "to", "create", "animated", "Lego", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJR", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Well, it took hundreds of people, four years to make it so it was insanely difficult.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "took", "hundreds", "of", "people", ",", "four", "years", "to", "make", "it", "so", "it", "was", "insanely", "difficult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phil"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Is that hard because normally, there's like one director, right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "hard", "because", "normally", ",", "there", "'s", "like", "one", "director", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "We never fight.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "never", "fight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christopher Miller"]}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "Who the hell was the biggest diva (ph) of all those?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "the", "hell", "was", "the", "biggest", "diva", "(", "ph", ")", "of", "all", "those", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Christopher Miller was the huge diva.", "answer_tokens": ["Christopher", "Miller", "was", "the", "huge", "diva", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "I'm doing the red carpet for CNN on Sunday March 2nd, what are you tips -- is it a win best movie do you think?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "the", "red", "carpet", "for", "CNN", "on", "Sunday", "March", "2nd", ",", "what", "are", "you", "tips", "--", "is", "it", "a", "win", "best", "movie", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CD", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "JJS", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "Gosh.", "answer_tokens": ["Gosh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday March 2nd"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "What's been the best movie you've seen recently?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "best", "movie", "you", "'ve", "seen", "recently", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Honestly, you know, they're also different but we were talking before about the Wolf of Wall Street.", "answer_tokens": ["Honestly", ",", "you", "know", ",", "they", "'re", "also", "different", "but", "we", "were", "talking", "before", "about", "the", "Wolf", "of", "Wall", "Street", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "It flies by, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "flies", "by", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "Walmart?", "question_tokens": ["Walmart", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "Jobless, I think homeless and falling sleep on my desk, pretty ignominious end to one of the great careers on American TV.", "answer_tokens": ["Jobless", ",", "I", "think", "homeless", "and", "falling", "sleep", "on", "my", "desk", ",", "pretty", "ignominious", "end", "to", "one", "of", "the", "great", "careers", "on", "American", "TV", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]